{"first":{"question":"You wake up in the morning. Your dog comes to you.","background":"background_2","person":"null","face":"null","fore":"fore_11","answers":["You pet your dog and praise it","You first feed your dog and then take it for a walk","You first take your dog for a walk and then feed it","You scold your dog and keep sleeping"],"You pet your dog and praise it":"rapsutus","You first feed your dog and then take it for a walk":"aamun jälkeen","You first take your dog for a walk and then feed it":"aamun jälkeen","You scold your dog and keep sleeping":"pommi","You pet your dog and praise itColor":"green","You first feed your dog and then take it for a walkColor":"green","You first take your dog for a walk and then feed itColor":"green","You scold your dog and keep sleepingColor":"red"},"aamun jälkeen":{"question":"Your dog eats its food with pleasure and pees and poops outside. Your dog comes to you with a toy.","background":"background_8","person":"null","face":"null","fore":"fore_11","answers":["You get angry at the dog for begging for attention and you don't play with it","You play with the dog for a while and then do something else","You play with the dog for a couple of hours","You play with the dog for an hour"],"You get angry at the dog for begging for attention and you don't play with it":"ennen päivälenkkiä","You play with the dog for a while and then do something else":"ennen päivälenkkiä","You play with the dog for a couple of hours":"ennen päivälenkkiä","You play with the dog for an hour":"ennen päivälenkkiä","You get angry at the dog for begging for attention and you don't play with itColor":"red","You play with the dog for a while and then do something elseColor":"green","You play with the dog for a couple of hoursColor":"yellow","You play with the dog for an hourColor":"green"},"rapsutus":{"question":"Your dog's tail wags happily and its back leg moves up and down.","background":"background_2","person":"null","face":"null","fore":"fore_11","answers":["You first feed your dog and then take it for a walk","You first take your dog for a walk and then feed it","You find that the dog does not need anything else and continue to sleep"],"You first feed your dog and then take it for a walk":"aamun jälkeen","You first take your dog for a walk and then feed it":"aamun jälkeen","You find that the dog does not need anything else and continue to sleep":"pommi","You first feed your dog and then take it for a walkColor":"green","You first take your dog for a walk and then feed itColor":"green","You find that the dog does not need anything else and continue to sleepColor":"red"},"pommi":{"question":"You accidentally sleep too many hours and hear your dog whining in another room.","background":"background_1","person":"null","face":"null","fore":"fore_11","answers":["You feed your dog and take it out for a walk","You just can't get out of bed, so you keep on sleeping"],"You feed your dog and take it out for a walk":"ennen päivälenkkiä","You just can't get out of bed, so you keep on sleeping":"laiminlyönti","You feed your dog and take it out for a walkColor":"green","You just can't get out of bed, so you keep on sleepingColor":"red"},"laiminlyönti":{"question":"Your dog has peed and pooped on the floor. The dog looks really sad.","background":"background_5","person":"null","face":"null","fore":"fore_11","answers":["You get angry at your dog and in your anger, you sleep the rest of the day","You think that you are not suitable to be a dog owner and sell your dog away","You pet your dog, apologize to it, feed it and take it out for a evening walk"],"You get angry at your dog and in your anger, you sleep the rest of the day":"null","You think that you are not suitable to be a dog owner and sell your dog away":"null","You pet your dog, apologize to it, feed it and take it out for a evening walk":"null","You get angry at your dog and in your anger, you sleep the rest of the dayColor":"red","You think that you are not suitable to be a dog owner and sell your dog awayColor":"yellow","You pet your dog, apologize to it, feed it and take it out for a evening walkColor":"green"},"ennen päivälenkkiä":{"question":"It's almost three o'clock. Your dog comes to you.","background":"background_1","person":"null","face":"null","fore":"fore_11","answers":["You wait for a couple of hours and then take it out for a walk","You take your dog out for a walk","You go to town without your dog and spend the rest of the day there"],"You wait for a couple of hours and then take it out for a walk":"päivälenkki","You take your dog out for a walk":"päivälenkki","You go to town without your dog and spend the rest of the day there":"laiminlyönti","You wait for a couple of hours and then take it out for a walkColor":"green","You take your dog out for a walkColor":"green","You go to town without your dog and spend the rest of the day thereColor":"red"},"päivälenkki":{"question":"You take your dog out for a walk. The dog pees and poops outside. You come across an unknown dog and its owner.","background":"background_3","person":"character_7","face":"face_happy","fore":"null","answers":["You keep your dog's leash long and let it run towards the other dog","You take your dog closer and ask the other dog owner if her dog can be greeted","You take your dog close and don't let it greet the other dog"],"You keep your dog's leash long and let it run towards the other dog":"vihainen koira","You take your dog closer and ask the other dog owner if her dog can be greeted":"iloinen koira","You take your dog close and don't let it greet the other dog":"päivälenkin jälkeen","You keep your dog's leash long and let it run towards the other dogColor":"red","You take your dog closer and ask the other dog owner if her dog can be greetedColor":"green","You take your dog close and don't let it greet the other dogColor":"yellow"},"vihainen koira":{"question":"Oncoming dog attacks your dog.","background":"background_3","person":"character_7","face":"face_sad","fore":"null","answers":["You get angry at the owner of the other dog, threaten to call the police and continue your walk","You quickly pull your dog towards you, apologize that you did not keep your dog close and continue your walk"],"You get angry at the owner of the other dog, threaten to call the police and continue your walk":"päivälenkin jälkeen","You quickly pull your dog towards you, apologize that you did not keep your dog close and continue your walk":"päivälenkin jälkeen","You get angry at the owner of the other dog, threaten to call the police and continue your walkColor":"red","You quickly pull your dog towards you, apologize that you did not keep your dog close and continue your walkColor":"green"},"iloinen koira":{"question":"Your dog greets the other dog. Both of the dogs wag their tails happily.","background":"background_3","person":"character_7","face":"face_happy","fore":"null","answers":["You chat with the other dog owner and continue your walk","You don't chat with the other dog owner and continue your walk"],"You chat with the other dog owner and continue your walk":"päivälenkin jälkeen","You don't chat with the other dog owner and continue your walk":"päivälenkin jälkeen","You chat with the other dog owner and continue your walkColor":"green","You don't chat with the other dog owner and continue your walkColor":"green"},"päivälenkin jälkeen":{"question":"Your dog comes to you after the walk.","background":"background_1","person":"null","face":"null","fore":"fore_11","answers":["You feed your dog and play with it","You feed your dog and then do something else without your dog","You wait for couple of hours and then feed your dog","You will no longer feed your dog today"],"You feed your dog and play with it":"ennen iltalenkkiä","You feed your dog and then do something else without your dog":"ennen iltalenkkiä","You wait for couple of hours and then feed your dog":"ennen iltalenkkiä","You will no longer feed your dog today":"ennen iltalenkkiä","You feed your dog and play with itColor":"green","You feed your dog and then do something else without your dogColor":"green","You wait for couple of hours and then feed your dogColor":"green","You will no longer feed your dog todayColor":"red"},"ennen iltalenkkiä":{"question":"It's getting close to evening time. Your dog comes to you.","background":"background_5","person":"null","face":"null","fore":"fore_11","answers":["You take your dog for an evening walk","You go to sleep","You give your dog an extra portion of food, take it out for a walk and go to sleep"],"You take your dog for an evening walk":"null","You go to sleep":"null","You give your dog an extra portion of food, take it out for a walk and go to sleep":"null","You take your dog for an evening walkColor":"green","You go to sleepColor":"red","You give your dog an extra portion of food, take it out for a walk and go to sleepColor":"yellow"},"lopetus":{"question":"You come home from the evening walk. Your dog seems happy. You are already very tired, so you prepare going to sleep and go to your bed.","background":"background_5","person":"null","face":"null","fore":"fore_11","answers":["You think that it is nice to own a dog","You find owning a dog tough, so you try to find a good new home for your dog","You think that owning a dog is worth this hard work"],"You think that it is nice to own a dog":"null","You find owning a dog tough, so you try to find a good new home for your dog":"null","You think that owning a dog is worth this hard work":"null","You think that it is nice to own a dogColor":"green","You find owning a dog tough, so you try to find a good new home for your dogColor":"yellow","You think that owning a dog is worth this hard workColor":"green"}}